<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Birdhouse</title><link>https://kestrelv84.net</link><description>Kestrel&apos;s blog and stuff</description><item><title>act-ii</title><link>https://kestrelv84.net/posts/Act-II.html</link><description><![CDATA[<h3>Session VIII (05/02/2026)</h3>
<p>So the PCs have just lifted a blade ship and some mysterious boxes or something from a random asteroid on the edge of the blacksphere. Then they get jumped by five shardships.</p>
]]></description><guid>https://kestrelv84.net/posts/Act-II.html</guid></item><item><title>brainstorming</title><link>https://kestrelv84.net/posts/Brainstorming.html</link><description><![CDATA[<h1>Places to borrow ideas from</h1>
<ul>
<li>Spelljammer, obviously</li>
<li>HSR for the large-scale organisations, structure of the universe type deal, weird shit, and perhaps the concept of aeons</li>
<li>Arcane's version of hextech for the magitech vibes</li>
<li>Starburst galaxies are awesome and I want one (see wikipedia)</li>
<li>ZZZ for hollows (I have no imagination apparently)</li>
</ul>
<h1>Worldbuilding</h1>
<h2>Mechanics</h2>
<p>This stuff is how the world physically functions - most importantly, the rules governing magic. Doesn't have to make a lot of sense but more is better.</p>
<h3>Stellar Physics</h3>
<p>Without the interference of humans, gods or any other creatures, stellar physics works as normal. Stars go through seqences, you've got black holes, all types of planets, et cetera. Stars are the normal distances away from each other in realspace aka wildspace, galaxies exist, there's a galactic core where there are a lot of stars much closer together than you'll find in the outer circles.</p>
]]></description><guid>https://kestrelv84.net/posts/Brainstorming.html</guid></item><item><title>Enemies</title><link>https://kestrelv84.net/posts/Enemies.html</link><description><![CDATA[<h3>General Features</h3>
<p>All remnants can be controlled by a person of sufficient power using a specialised spell (details coming soon.)</p>
]]></description><guid>https://kestrelv84.net/posts/Enemies.html</guid></item><item><title>about</title><link>https://kestrelv84.net/posts/about.html</link><description><![CDATA[<h2>About the birdhouse</h2>
]]></description><guid>https://kestrelv84.net/posts/about.html</guid></item></channel></rss>
